(Amy:)Hey. They may conceive a child
on their wedding night.
(Amy:)Don't you think the kid might get a kick
out of knowing how it happened?
l don't care. Ask her things like,
"Are you gonna take Howard's name?"
Not "who's gonna sit on who?"
l've been thinking I'm gonna hyphenate.
Bernadette Maryann
Rostenkowski-Wolowitz.
Nice. You should totally get Bernadette
Maryann Rostenkowski-wolowitz.com...
(Penny:)...before someone snaps it up.
(Bernadette:)Howard already took care of it.
(Bernadette:)He set up our beautiful wedding website
with cute facts...
(Bernadette:)...about our family histories.
(Bernadette:)For a while in Poland, my family
and his family were neighbors.
- Oh, that's cool.
- No, it's not. I'll explain it to you later.
(Raj:)May I have your attention, please?
We are here tonight to celebrate
the upcoming nuptials of my best friend...
(Raj:)...Howard Wolowitz.
(Raj:)Hear, hear.